Guide to the Harry Adams Photographs
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Identified Subjects, 1951–1985
  - Entertainers and Entertainment Events
    - Peck, Gregory, and Veronique Passani Peck
      - Interior view of Gregory Peck and Veronique Passani Peck with Yvonne Brathwaite Burke and others at a banquet, circa 1965; 3 photographic prints (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Quinn, Anthony
      - Interior portrait of Anthony Quinn with two women and two men, circa 1970 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Ray Anthony Orchestra
      - View of two performers dressed as ancient Greeks performing a comic skit with members of the Ray Anthony Orchestra watching them, circa 1955 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - Rogers, Roy
      - Exterior portrait of Roy Rogers and a man holding a movie camera, circa 1953 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Rolle, Esther
      - Interior portrait of Esther Rolle and Ted Lange with two women and a man, circa 1975 (Box 3, Folder 173)
      - Interior views of women and men at an event including Esther Rolle and Kareem Abdul-Jabbar, 1977 December; 2 photographic prints (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Ross, Diana
      - Interior portraits of Diana Ross with others, 1973 June; 3 photographic prints (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Sinatra, Frank
      - Interior portraits of Frank Sinatra, including a portrait with Leon Washington, 1966 March 20-25; 3 photographic prints (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Speed, Carol
      - Interior portrait of Carol Speed with prizes related to a promotion at a bank and her film, "Abby", 1974 November 25 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Sutton, Frank
      - Interior portrait of Frank Sutton wearing a United States Marine Corps uniform and a man wearing a United States Navy uniform, 1967 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Thomas, Danny
      - Interior portraits of Danny Thomas and others at the Los Angeles Biltmore Hotel, 1964 November; 4 photographic portraits (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Van Dyke, Dick
      - Exterior views of Dick Van Dyke at a political rally for Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich) Rockefeller, which includes an exterior portrait of Van Dyke with Margerie Willett Van Dyke, 1964 May; 4 photographic prints (Box 3, Folder 180)
      - Interior portraits of Dick Van Dyke and others at the Ebony Showcase Theatre, 1965 June; 3 photographic prints (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Whyte, Leroy, and his Orchestra
      - Interior portrait of the orchestra of Leroy "Snake" Whyte, 1954 December; 2 photographic prints (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Wonder, Stevie
      - Interior portrait of Stevie Wonder at the KJLH 103.3 radio station in Los Angeles, California, 1980 October 3 (Box 3, Folder 183)
      - Interior portrait of Stevie Wonder and a man, probably during an event at a church, 1981 January (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Journalists and Authors
    - Baldwin, James
      - Interior portraits of James Baldwin with others, 1964 February; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Greater Los Angeles Press Club
      - Interior portrait of three men at a meeting of the Greater Los Angeles Press Club, 1976 May (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Haley, Alex
      - Interior portraits of Alex Haley including an image with another man, 1976 October; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Lerutte, Harry
      - Exterior portrait of Harry Lerutte wearing a press pass for the 1959 World Series, Los Angeles, California, 1959 October; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - McCormick, Larry
      - Interior portrait of Larry McCormick and three women, 1974 May 17 (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - McGee, Paul C.
      - Interior portrait of Louis V. Cole and two other men presenting a certificate and check to Paul C. McGee, 1967 December (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Nader, Ralph
      - Interior views of Ralph Nader with others, 1969 October 23; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Orr, Wini
      - Interior portrait of Wini Orr and a man, 1962 July (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Pye, Brad, Jr.
      - Interior portrait of Jim Healy, Brad Pye, Jr., and another man at a banquet honoring Pye at the Rodger Young Auditorium, Los Angeles, California, 1966 January (Box 4, Folder 193)
      - Interior portrait of Brad Pye, Jr., with two men holding Pall Mall cigarettes, probably in the offices of the Los Angeles Sentinel newspaper, circa 1970 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Robinson, Edward
      - Interior portrait of Edward "Abie" Robinson and a woman, 1976 January; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 195)
      - Interior portrait of two women and two men, including Edward "Abie" Robinson, 1977 July (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Washington, Leon
      - Interior portrait of Leon Washington with a woman and two men with an award from the National Newspaper Publishers Association, 1972 January (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - Judges, Attorneys, and Law Enforcement
    - Cochran, Johnnie
      - Interior portrait of Johnnie Cochran with Barbara Deadwyler and another man, 1966 March; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 198)
      - Interior portrait of a Melodie Cochran cutting a birthday cake with Johnnie Cochran and Jean Cochran, 1973 January (Box 4, Folder 199)
      - Interior portrait of five attorneys, including Johnnie Cochran, 1973 March (Box 4, Folder 200)
      - Interior portrait of three men, including Johnnie Cochran sitting on a throne-like chair, 1973 March (Box 4, Folder 201)
      - Interior portrait of Johnnie Cochran with a girl, woman, and two men, 1974 December (Box 4, Folder 202)
      - Exterior portrait of a large group of two women and twenty-seven men, including Johnnie L. Cochran, probably posed in front of Ross Plaza Professional Center at 1818 South Western Avenue, Los Angeles, California, circa 1974 (Box 4, Folder 203)
      - Interior portrait of Johnnie Cochran, 1976 April; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 204)
      - Interior view of Johnnie Cochran and a male judge taking the oath to become the Los Angeles County District Attorney, circa 1978 (Box 4, Folder 205)
      - Interior views and portraits of an event at the Los Angeles Biltmore Hotel, including Johnnie Cochran, 1980 March 15-16; 8 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 206)
      - Interior portrait of Johnnie Cochran, circa 1980 (Box 4, Folder 207)
      - Interior portrait of Johnnie Cochran with two men, circa 1982 (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Criminal Courts Bar Association
      - Interior portraits during an awards banquet for the Criminal Courts Bar Association, including Joseph M. Rosen and Kathleen Parker, 1967 February; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Cunningham, David
      - Interior portrait of David Cunningham, 1967 March (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - Foreman, Percy
      - Interior views of Percy Foreman at a podium at the Los Angeles Biltmore Hotel, 1964 March 28; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - Los Angeles Police Department
      - Exterior views of members of the Los Angeles Police Department SWAT (Special Weapons and Tactics, a militarized police unit) team during a standoff with members of the Black Panther Party at its Southern California Headquarters, 4115 South Central Avenue, Los Angeles, California, 1969 December 8; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 212)
      - Exterior portrait of three male members of the Los Angeles Police Department Motorcycle Drill Team mounted on three motorcycles each with a child, including two girls and a boy, circa 1980 (Box 4, Folder 213)
      - Exterior portrait of Tom Bradley with a group of officers from the Los Angeles Police Department, circa 1980 (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - Los Angeles Sheriff Department
      - Interior portrait of members of the Los Angeles Sheriff Department, including deputies Ramsay and Foreman, circa 1960 (Box 4, Folder 215)
      - Interior view of four members of the Los Angeles Sheriff Department carrying an emotional man as well as another man viewing the group, circa 1960; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 216)
      - View of an information table for the Los Angeles Sheriff Department at an event, 1966 August 14 (Box 4, Folder 217)
      - Interior portrait of a man with a female and a male member of the Los Angeles County Sheriff at a Sunday Morning Breakfast Club meeting, 1966 December 10 (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Lloyd, Charles Earl
      - Exterior portrait of Charles Earl Lloyd speaking on a telephone installed in a Mercedes Benz automobile from the automobile dealership of Peter Satori, Pasadena, California, 1973 June (Box 4, Folder 219)
      - Interior portraits of Charles Earl Lloyd and others, 1975 October; 5 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 220)
      - Interior portraits of Charles Earl Lloyd, 1975 November; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 221)
      - Interior portrait of Charles Lloyd and a woman, circa 1975 (Box 4, Folder 222)
      - Interior portrait of Charles Lloyd with two women, circa 1975 (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - Miller, Loren
      - Interior portraits of Loren Miller with others at an event, circa 1962; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 224)
      - Studio portrait of Loren Miller, 1963 January 20 (Box 4, Folder 225)
      - Interior portrait of Loren Miller with two women, circa 1965 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - National Association of Women Judges
      - Interior portraits at the annual meeting of the National Association of Women Judges, including Jerry Brown with Betty Barteau as well as discrete images of Tom Bradley and Joan Dempsey Klein with others, 1979 October 25-28; 5 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - Oscar Joel Bryant Foundation
      - Interior portrait of Daryl Gates receiving an award from the Oscar Joel Bryant Foundation, 1972 March (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Spencer, Vaino Hassan
      - Interior portraits of Vaino Hassan Spencer, 1975 December 15; 2 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 229)
      - Interior portraits of Vaino Hassan Spencer and others at her swearing-in as a Los Angeles County Superior Court Judge, 1976 November; 3 photographic prints (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - Wives of the Bench and Bar
      - Interior portrait of two women holding a commendation from the city of Los Angeles to the Wives of the Bench and Bar, 1975 March (Box 4, Folder 231)
  - Los Angeles Personalities, Groups, and Events
    - Africa Travel Association
      - Interior views at a meeting of the Africa Travel Association, 1979 May 20-25; 6 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - American Woodmen
      - Interior portrait of four female members of the American Woodmen wearing fezzes and sashes, 1966 May 24 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Calloway, Bill, and Bill Muse
      - Interior portraits at a banquet honoring Bill Calloway and Bill Muse at the Los Angeles Biltmore Hotel, which includes Jerry Brown, 1973 August; 12 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Cohn, Nudie
      - Exterior views of a 1975 Cadillac Eldorado decorated with horseshoes and guns created and owned by Nudie Cohn, circa 1980; 2 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Collins, Paul, and Carl Owens
      - Indoor portrait of men and women with paintings depicting Shaka Zulu created by Paul Collins and Afonso I of Kongo created by Carl Owens, 1978 January; 2 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Courtney, C. S.
      - Interior portraits of attendees of an event, including the presentation of a portrait of a boy by C. S. Courtney, 1970 May 1; 3 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Curtis, Chuck
      - Interior view of Chuck Curtis and an other man with a display advertising the printing service offered by Curtis, circa 1970 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Daniel Hale Williams Medical Center
      - Exterior portrait of seven men in front of the Daniel Hale Williams Medical Center in the Watts neighborhood of Los Angeles, circa 1980 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Dunn, William M.
      - Exterior portrait of William M. Dunn in his uniform from the United States 10th Cavalry with others, including Lenton W. Glascow and Woody Strode, related to an unrealized film or an episode of the television show "The High Chaparral,", 1967 November; 5 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Dunn, Zephra
      - Interior portrait of two women, including Zephra Dunn, and a man, 1985 April; 2 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Echo Barber Shop
      - Interior view of a broken window in the Echo Barber Shop owned by Harry Adams at the intersection of Central Avenue and 43rd Street, Los Angeles, California, 1975 November (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Elizabeth II
      - Exterior views of a visit by Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, and Prince Philip, her consort, which includes the royals as well as Tom Bradley, 1983 February 28; 7 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Enterprise Savings and Loan Association
      - Exterior portrait of three men posed in front of the Enterprise Savings and Loan Association branch office in Bedford, California, 1976 July (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States
      - Interior portrait of two men, one man receiving a manager of the month award for September 1969 from the Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States, Henry Dymond Agency, 1969 September (Box 5, Folder 245)
        Photograph printed backwards
    - Feminine Touch, Inc.
      - Interior portraits related to an awards event, which include a woman and a man presenting an award to George R. Hymer, III, on behalf of the Feminine Touch, Inc., 1966 November 12; 2 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Freedman, Marty
      - Interior portrait of Marty Freedman, owner of Mister Marty of California clothing, receiving an award for "best eyeglass wearer of the world," from seven women related to a modeling school, circa 1970; 2 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - George Washington Preparatory High School
      - Interior portrait of four women and two men, probably a classroom at George Washington Preparatory High School, 1975 January 30 (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - Greek Letter Societies
      - Interior portrait of two women and a man at an African American fraternity and sorority event at the International Hotel, Los Angeles, California, 1967 February (Box 5, Folder 249)
      - Interior portrait of six women and a man at a banquet for the Founders' Day of the Delta Sigma Theta sorority, 1973 January (Box 5, Folder 250)
      - Interior portraits from a award banquet for the Delta Sigma Theta sorority, which includes an award given by Tom Bradley and Ethel Bradley to Zephyr Chisom Carter as well as awards given to Nancy Wilson and others, 1975 January 25; 5 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 251)
      - Interior portrait of thirteen men, members of the Kappa Alpha Psi fraternity, 1976 September (Box 5, Folder 252)
      - Interior portrait of a woman and three men at an event for the Alpha Kappa Alpha sorority, Alpha Gamma Omega Chapter, at the Century Plaza Hotel, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Gunn, Kathryn
      - Interior portrait of Kathryn Gunn and a man, the latter pouring a Hamm's beer into her glass, 1963 July (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - Harris, Margaret
      - Interior portrait of Margaret Harris with two women and a man, probably at the Los Angeles International Airport, 1965 August 23 (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - Hollywood Roosevelt Hotel
      - Interior portraits of groups of men at an event at the Hollywood Roosevelt Hotel in Los Angeles, California, 1978 January; 4 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - Ike
      - Exterior view of an automobile with a man, identified as Ike, with a group of chickens; a sign on the automobile, "Ike can tame any chicken", circa 1960 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Itkin, Mikhail F., and Larry L. Lawrence
      - Interior view of Mikhail F. Itkin and Larry L. Lawrence with their attorney, Albert L. Gordon, attempting to obtain a marriage license at the Los Angeles County Clerk's office surrounded by journalists, 1977 March 15 (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - Johnson's Bathhouse
      - Interior and exterior portraits of Robert Lee Elder and Rose Harper with Virginia Johnson at Johnson's Bathhouse and Health Spa in Los Angeles, 1977 January; 2 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Jones, Vessa
      - Interior portrait of Vessa Jones, 1969 December 19 (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - Miss U.S. Talented Teen Pageant & Revue
      - Interior portraits related to the Hal Jackson's Miss U.S. Talented Teen Pageant & Revue, which includes winners Denise DuMaine and an unidentified Miss California, 1974 July; 2 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 261)
    - Morehouse College Alumni Association
      - Interior portrait of nine men at a Morehouse College Alumni Association, Los Angeles Chapter, banquet, 1973 May (Box 5, Folder 262)
    - National Association of Letter Carriers
      - Interior portrait of women and a man at an event for the National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 34, 1975 December; 3 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 263)
    - National Schools
      - Interior portraits presentation of certificates from National Schools for a course in air conditioning and refrigeration servicing to Vernon Marion Hemingway and others, 1967 February 17; 6 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 264)
    - National Society of Real Estate Appraisers
      - Interior portraits at a banquet for the National Society of Real Estate Appraisers, California Chapter, including Rick Kelly and Billy Mills, 1975 February 14; 3 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - Olympics
      - Interior portrait of a woman and Sam the Eagle, the mascot for the 1984 Olympics, 1984 April (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - Parade
      - Exterior views of a parade that includes of a float for McDonald's restaurant, which includes Ronald McDonald, Officer Big Mac, and Captain Crook, and a view of a marching band, circa 1975; 2 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - Phoenix Man Realtors
      - Interior portrait of three men with one man holding a display for Phoenix Man Realtors, 1974 December 15 (Box 5, Folder 268)
    - Ramos, Jackie
      - Interior portrait of women having tea, including Jackie Ramos, circa 1975; 5 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 269)
    - Roberts, Lawrence
      - Interior portrait of Lawrence Roberts with a woman and two men, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 270)
    - Robinson's Research and Enterprises
      - Interior portrait of 15 women and 12 men who completed a course in employee-management relations at Robinson's Research and Enterprises, 1965 March 12 (Box 5, Folder 271)
    - Sanders, Joseph Stanley
      - Interior portraits of three men, including Joseph Stanley Sanders, 1962 December; 2 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 272)
      - Exterior view of a Joseph Stanley Sanders with his parents in a convertible automobile during a parade in the Watts neighborhood of Los Angeles, California, 1963 September (Box 5, Folder 273)
    - Sendai, Japan
      - Interior portrait of four women and six men related to the promotion of Sendai, Japan, related to liquor distribution, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 274)
    - Soror, Iam
      - Interior portrait of Bill Howard presenting a framed card to Iam Soror with Joey Williams and a woman, circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 275)
    - Tinker, Mrs.
      - Interior portrait of Mrs. Tinker, holding a birthday letter from the Social Security Administration, with a man, 1973 May (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - Watson, Earl
      - Interior portrait of Earl "The Pearl" Watson after receiving an award with Melba Rose Watson, five girls, and six boys, circa 1975 (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - Williams, John L.
      - Interior views from a banquet honoring John L. Williams by a labor group, 1978 January; 2 photographic prints (Box 5, Folder 278)
  - Politicians and Political Events
    - Bradley, Ethel Arnold
      - Interior portrait of three women, including Ethel Arnold Bradley, holding a large piece of fabric, 1973 May (Box 6, Folder 279)
      - Interior portrait of Ethel Arnold Bradley with three women, circa 1973 (Box 6, Folder 280)
      - Interior portrait of Ethel Arnold Bradley at an event, 1976 August (Box 6, Folder 281)
      - Interior portrait of Ethel Arnold Bradley with Kenneth Hahn and woman, 1980 May 9 (Box 6, Folder 282)
      - Interior portrait of Ethel Arnold Bradley being kissed on her cheeks by Sammy Davis and another man, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 283)
      - Interior portrait of Ethel Arnold Bradley and man holding two packages of "C" Loaf, 1985 June (Box 6, Folder 284)
    - Bradley, Ethel Arnold, and Tom Bradley
      - Exterior portrait of Ethel Arnold Bradley and Tom Bradley, circa 1962 (Box 6, Folder 285)
      - Interior portrait of Ethel Arnold Bradley, Tom Bradley, three women, and three men, probably at a banquet, 1974 May 24 (Box 6, Folder 286)
      - Interior portrait of Ethel Arnold Bradley and Tom Bradley with a woman and man, possibly the bride and groom at a wedding, 1975 July (Box 6, Folder 287)
      - Interior portrait of Ethel Arnold Bradley and Tom Bradley with a woman and a man, circa 1977; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 288)
      - Interior portrait of Ethel Arnold Bradley and Tom Bradley with Yvonne Brathwaite Burke and another woman, circa 1977 (Box 6, Folder 289)
      - View of an audience that includes Ethel Arnold Bradley and Tom Bradley, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 290)
      - Interior portrait of Ethel Arnold Bradley and Tom Bradley with a woman and two men, including a priest, at an event, 1981 January (Box 6, Folder 291)
      - Interior portrait of Ethel Arnold Bradley and Tom Bradley with a woman, circa 1982 (Box 6, Folder 292)
    - Bradley, Tom
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley and two men, circa 1960-1965 (Box 6, Folder 293)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with a man, probably in a clothing store, circa 1962 (Box 6, Folder 294)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley and another man addressing a group at the Los Angeles City Hall, 1965 May 3 (Box 6, Folder 295)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with four men including Billy Mills, circa 1965 (Box 6, Folder 296)
      - Exterior portraits of mourners, including Tom Bradley and Gilbert William Lindsay, leaving a memorial service from a church, 1967 February 3; 6 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 297)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with Mervyn M. Dymally, Frank Holman, Billy Mills, Leon D. Ralph at the Sheraton Wilshire Motor Inn, circa 1970 (Box 6, Folder 298)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with a woman, 1971 March 28 (Box 6, Folder 299)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with three women and two men, 1973 January (Box 6, Folder 300)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with seven women and a man, 1973 April (Box 6, Folder 301)
      - Interior portraits of Tom Bradley and others, 1973 April; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 302)
      - Interior portraits of Tom Bradley and others at a banquet, 1973 July; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 303)
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with a young woman, 1973 December (Box 6, Folder 304)
      - Exterior view of a group with a cake, including Tom Bradley, Yvonne Brathwaite Burke, and Ted Watkins, 1974 October; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 305)
      - Interior portrait of Thomas Bradley with two men as well as Ted Brown with his painting of Martin Luther King, Jr., circa 1974 (Box 6, Folder 306)
      - Interior portraits of a woman celebrating her one hundredth birthday including a portrait with Tom Bradley, 1975 January 26; 2 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 307)
      - Interior portraits of women and men, including Tom Bradley, 1975 March; 5 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 308)
      - Interior and exterior views related to a funeral attended by Tom Bradley, 1975 September; 7 photographic prints (Box 6, Folder 309)
      - Exterior portrait of Tom Bradley and a man both wearing graduation caps and gowns, circa 1975 (Box 6, Folder 310)